女士们与女服务员们
Ladies and waitresses,
我就是大魔术师憨迪尼
I am the great Han-dini!
世上某个婚礼蛋糕顶上装饰品的
Somewhere there's a top of a wedding cake
新郎娃娃跑掉了
missing its groom.
我上周末重上驾校了
I went to traffic school this weekend
教练是个魔术师
and was taught by a magician.
我重回驾校的时候  教练是说单口相声的
My traffic school was taught by a comedian.
过程并不好笑  不过好歹知道了
It wasn't funny, but at least I saw
乔恩·拉威茨他最近在忙啥
what Jon Lovitz was up to.
是因为"小酌后驾车"被开单吗
Did you get a DWI?
又小又拙后驾车
Driving while itty-bitty?
我连闯了好几个红灯
I ran a series of red lights.
就为了去传闻中出现杰尼龟的地方抓神奇宝贝
I received word there had been a Squirtle sighting.
现在  我要从帽子里
And now, I'm about to pull a rabbit
-变出一只兔兔  -有啥了不起
-out of a hat. -Big deal.
我刚还从厕所变出半只浣熊呢
I just pulled half a raccoon out of the toilet.
急急如律令
Presto!
悲催到要"令"我泪如雨下了
This is making me depressed-o.
小兔兔你去哪啦
Where are you?
上菜
Pick up.
兔子沙拉
Salad with a rabbit on it.
他的"夹毛"沙拉总是让人想"兔"
He just can't serve a salad without a hare in it.
天大好消息
Amazing news:
我捡到了一分钱
I found a penny.
还有  我们的甜品酒吧上了知名杂志啦
And our dessert bar is in Time Out Magazine.
"披萨鼠  你们都到哪去了"
"Where are they now? Pizza Rat!"
不是那篇  我们的报导
Not that. Our piece is right here
是在《行尸走肉》广告隔壁这篇
next to this Walking Dead ad.
不对  不是广告  是迈克·道格拉斯
Oh, wait, that's Michael Douglas.
那的确是行尸走肉没错
So, the walking dead.
"前丑闻女王卡洛琳·钱宁
"Former scandal queen Caroline Channing's
布鲁克林的温馨甜品酒吧"麦与卡" 美..."
cozy Brooklyn dessert bar, M&C's, that's beaut--"
"卡洛琳·钱宁的甜品酒吧"吗
"Caroline Channing's dessert bar"?
卡洛琳  这店又不是你的性生活
This place isn't like your sex life, Caroline.
不是全靠你自己"一手"撑起
You're not doing it all by yourself.
我现在都不跟自己"性生活"了
I don't even do it by myself anymore.
嫌弃自己这个炮友话太多
I was talking too much,
你看  我在这里提起了你呢
and, look, I mentioned you right here.
"搭档"
"Partner."
我不只是搭档
I'm more than just the partner,
我是一切创作灵感的来源
I'm the creative inspiration.
就好比我是乔布斯
I'm Steve Jobs
而你是他那个骑着代步车的胖子搭档
and you're the fat guy that drives a Segway.
我试过让你参与进来
I tried to include you.
我跟你说过访问是在周一
I told you the interview was on Monday,
但你说周一夜是你的笑气夜
and you said that's your whippit night.
我的确笑了呢
Oh, I whipped it.
吸到嗨得不行
Whipped it good.
卡洛琳  拜托你大屁股挪远点
Caroline, back that ass up.
我不想别人太接近我的宝宝
I don't want anyone too close to my baby.
所以你把她泡香水里  把别人熏跑吗
Is that why you dipped her in perfume?
我希望大家对待芭芭拉宝宝
I want everyone to treat little Barbara
就像对女星玛丽亚·凯莉一样
like Mariah Carey
并敬畏到不敢直视她双眼
and never look directly in her eyes.
所以你让她戴墨镜吗
Is that why she's wearing sunglasses?
我刚"完事儿"
I just got off.
上班也是刚完事儿
And also, I'm done with work.
我的女人们
There's my girls.
奥列格  我们才不是你的女人
We're not your girls, Oleg.
我可是有来自法官的书面证明
I have it in writing from a judge.
奥列格  别离她太近
Oleg, give her some space.
她的美黑都还没干呢
Her spray tan hasn't even dried yet.
苏菲  我最近在读一个育儿的博客
Sophie, I've been reading a parenting blog called
名叫"这下毁了自己人生了吧"
"So, You've Ruined Your Life,"
上面写  孩子父亲与孩子建立感情十分重要
and they say it's very important for a dad to bond with his baby.
这只对人类父亲有效
I think that's only true for human dads.
你可以跟宝宝之后再建立感情
Maybe you can bond with the baby later.
比如等到她生了宝宝之后
You know, like, when she has a baby.
我等不了12年
I can't wait 12 years.
苏菲  我是她爸爸
Sophie, I'm her father.
她的诞生  我出了"材料"
I helped make her.
又不是圣母玛丽亚斯基  处女怀孕
This wasn't a Virgin Marski situation.
你们这对的"结合"  跟纯洁差了十万八千里
There was nothing immaculate about this conception.
好玩的部分已经结束了
Well, the fun part's over now.
她是我的
Yeah, she's mine.
好狗不挡路
Excuse you.
她推车技术越来越纯熟了啊
She's getting really good with that thing.
所有让我别接近她们的女人
I'm gonna do what I do when all women tell me
老子都会做一件事
not to be near them.
跟踪她
I'm gonna follow her.
卡洛琳·钱宁吗
Uh, Caroline Channing?
你好  我叫道格·雷诺兹  沃顿的教授
Hi, I'm Doug Reynolds, I'm a professor at Wharton.
我以前也在沃顿商学院上学
Hey, I went to Wharton.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我在杂志上读到了你的访问
I saw your interview in Time Out.
你提了好多次呢
You mentioned it several times.
其中一次是在人家问你甜品酒吧地点时
Once when you were asked where the dessert bar was located.
的确是在沃顿的东边啊
Well, it is east of Wharton.
你还没听到她的沃顿小曲呢
You haven't heard her Wharton song.
♪ 沃顿  沃顿  沃顿  沃顿 ♪
♪ Wharton, Wharton, Wharton, Wharton ♪
♪ 沃顿  沃顿  沃顿  沃顿  沃顿 ♪
♪ Wharton, Wharton, Wharton Wharton, Wharton ♪
还真不是什么好曲儿...
Yeah, it's not a great song,
但你摆脱父亲丑闻  涅槃重生
but the story about how you built your business
最终创业成功的故事
from the ashes of your father's infamy,
十分鼓舞人心
that's inspiring.
简直就是商界的《追梦赤子心》
You're the business world's Rudy.
你干嘛直接引用我的话来夸我啦
Well, now you're just quoting me.
你好  我是文中的"搭档"
Hi, I'm "Partner."
你好  搭档
Howdy, Partner.
我现在在宾大教商科
Hey, I teach a business class over at Penn
08年股市崩盘后我就沦落去那里了
because the stock market crashed in 2008.
我很希望能邀请到你们俩来
I would love it if both of you would come
跟我的学生们聊聊
and talk to the students.
是类似那种吓唬到不敢犯错吗
Like a scared-straight thing?
不是监狱[音似宾大]
Not the pen.
是宾大  宾夕法尼亚大学
Penn, the University of Pennsylvania.
沃顿是它的一个院系
That's where Wharton is.
如果你好好听我的沃顿小曲
If you'd listen to my whole song,
你会在第三段听到我有提
you'd hear it in the third verse.
我们会报销你们来费城的火车票
We'd pay for your train to Philadelphia
还有免费校园住宿
and campus housing.
我们很乐意去
We'd love to come.
对吧  搭档
Right, partner?
我的假释官
And my parole officer,
母亲  辅导员
mother, guidance counselor,
还有罗德岛州政府
and the state of Rhode Island
还说我这辈子进不了大学呢
said I'd never go to college.
我可以从网站上找到你的电邮
I can get your email from the website.
我再把资料发给你
I'll send you the info.
我们有网站啊
We have a site?
希望我们网站上没有放我的裸照
I hope there are no nudies of me on it
因为我的裸照肖像权卖给情色杂志老板了
'cause Larry Flynt owns the rights to my image.
你知道这代表什么吧
You know what this means?
♪ 沃顿  沃顿  沃顿  沃顿  沃顿 ♪
♪ Wharton, Wharton, Wharton, Wharton, Wharton ♪
♪ 沃顿  沃顿  沃顿  沃顿  沃顿... ♪
♪ Wharton, Wharton, Wharton, Wharton, Wharton, Wharton... ♪
带一个还两个大麻烟斗
One bong or two?
麦克斯  这是去出差
Max, this is a business trip.
又不是跟伍迪·哈里森去漫展
We're not going to Comic-Con with Woody Harrelson.
等等  真有这个选项吗
Wait, is that on the table?
你是为了甜品酒吧出差  我不是
Anyway, this is your trip for the dessert bar.
所以  带一个还两个
So again, one bong or two?
"搭档"这件事你是打算说我一辈子了是吧
I am never gonna live down the "Partner" thing, am I?
就像我为了救你  把"浴盐"扔了的事
Like when I threw away those bath salts to save your life.
我又没要啃掉你的脸
I wasn't gonna eat your face.
我不想再跟你吵这件事
I am not having this argument with you again.
我没有不爽搭档的事情
I'm not mad about the partner thing.
我对去大学可兴奋了  我已经告诉兰迪
I'm excited to go to college. I already told Randy,
他说他会送我一份上学大礼
and he's gonna send me a care package.
重点放在"大"
Emphasis on the package.
我之所以跟高中男友分手
I broke up with my high school boyfriend
为的就是能在大学里多挑挑
when I went to college just to keep my options open.
拜托  你可是跟披萨鼠出现在同期杂志的人
Pfft, you're in Time Out New York with Pizza Rat.
那个废柴现在能有多牛逼
What's that loser doing now?
他是马克·扎克伯格[脸书创办人]
It was Mark Zuckerberg.
跟我说说大学里的派对吧
Just tell me about the parties at college
我纯粹是因为这个才去的
'cause that's the only reason I'm going.
屌爆了
Oh, they were epic.
人们常说
You know what they say,
如果你能记得沃顿的每一个派对
if you remember the parties at Wharton,
那肯定是因为你没去过
you weren't there.
你是真的没去过  对吧
You weren't here, were you?
-没有  -好吧
-No. -Okay.
但好几个彻夜读书的夜晚
But some of those all-night study sessions
后来都"酒"劲挺强啊
got pretty punchy.
像打地鼠游戏这么有劲
Like whackadoo.
你让我也很想使劲给你一拳
You're making me punchy right now.
姑娘们
Hey, girls,
奥列格不在这里吧
Oleg isn't here, is he?
你有听到我们大叫"滚"或"把那玩意收起来"吗
Do you hear us screaming "Get out" or "Put that away"?
他一直不停想跟宝宝建立感情
He keeps wanting to bond with the baby.
他会什么就不能多像波兰的男人一点啊
Why can't he be more like the men in Poland?
我更想知道他为什么不能人在波兰
Why can't he be in Poland is my question.
那里的男人甚至都不乐意跟女儿同处一室
I mean, they wouldn't even be in the same room as their baby girl
除非到了卖女儿那天
until it was time to sell her off.
我父亲对我说的第一句话是
You know, my father's first words to me were,
"下一件拍卖物"
"Next item up for bid."
真不敢相信我会说这话
I can't believe I'm saying this,
但奥列格没有错啊
but Oleg's not wrong here.
尽管他其他地方全是错
He's wrong, literally, everywhere else.
肯定是奥列格
Oh, it must be Oleg.
-快把娘俩藏起来  -藏你们
- Hide us. - Hide you?
你的婴儿车大到从太空都能看见
That carriage can be seen from space.
告诉奥列格我绝对不在畜棚里
All right, tell Oleg I'm definitely not in the barn.
好了
Yeah, now,
我要去躲在畜棚里了
I'm gonna be in the barn.
这里就是我们安置硕士生
This is where we put up grad students
以及偶尔会有的
and occasional guest lecturers
没钱住酒店的客座教授
who are too poor to stay in a hotel.
废柴们
Losers.
你们有毛巾吗
You guys got any towels?
请原谅麦克斯的无礼
You'll have to forgive Max.
她只是太兴奋来到贵宝地
She's just excited to be here.
我们知道你们这里铁定会有
We know, obviously, there'll be a bath sheet
两人份的大浴巾以及擦手毛巾
and a hand towel for each of us.
对吧
Right?
这里就是你们的寝室
And here's your bedroom.
我是宿管  不过别担心
I'm the RA, but don't worry,
我不是那种超严肃的人
I'm not super uptight.
只要十点之后不发出噪音就行
Just no noise after 10:00
否则我会要你小命
or I'll come at you hard.
我们绝不会给你惹麻烦
You'll have no problems from us.
我以前在这里读书的时候也是宿管
I was an RA when I went to school here.
我是卡洛琳·钱宁
I'm Caroline Channing.
传说中的那位
The.
卡洛琳·钱宁
Caroline Channing?
传说中的扫兴鬼钱宁吗
You're Buzzkill Channing?
我就知道卡洛琳不是你的真名
I knew Caroline wasn't your real name.
你是我们这里神一般的宿管
You're the most legendary RA we've ever had.
我听说你有一次把学生从二楼窗口扔下楼
I heard you once threw a kid out of a second-story window.
那只是江湖谣言
That's just a myth,
但的确是有一个水烟筒被打飞了
but a hookah pipe did take flight.
而我也曾是机场附近的一名妓女[音似水烟]
And I was a hookah by the airport.
扫兴鬼大人造访  深感荣幸  蓬荜生辉
Well, it's an honor to have your here, Buzzkill.
你离开前我得先搜一遍你的垃圾袋
I'm gonna have to search your trash bag before you leave.
所有好东西都会藏在我屁眼里
Everything good's gonna be in my butt.
她这人真有趣
She's fun.
好了  来拿出行李吧
Okay, let's unpack,
分好我们各自的卫浴用品桶
get our shower buckets organized.
我行李都拿出来了  去派对啦
I'm unpacked. Let's go par-tois.
你带了几个酒壶啊
How many flasks do you have?
我都已经从你那里没收两个了
I already took two away from you.
来  你当观众
Now, you be the audience.
我得练习我明天的演讲
I need to practice my speech for tomorrow.
我们需要去派对
We need to party.
今晚必须以我们驾着警车
Tonight needs to end with us driving a police car
冲进学校中庭的喷水池里  不然就算没玩爽
into a fountain on the quad or it is a fail.
我不是来派对的
I am not here to party.
我是来...  来告诉大家
I am here to-- to show people
只要有决心和努力
with determination and perspiration,
你也能鼓舞别人
you can become an inspiration.
麦克斯  你觉得这句如何
Max, what do you think of that?
麦克斯
Max?
我才不帮你整理你的卫浴用品桶
I'm not organizing your shower bucket.
卡洛琳  你醒着吗
Caroline, are you awake?
没有
No.
没问题  她醒着  快进来
It's cool, she's up. Come on in.
这些人都是谁啊
Who are these people?
对不起啊  可是我们不得不离开酒吧
I'm sorry, but we had to leave the bar.
酒吧燃到爆了
The roof was on fire.
一开始我们以为DJ是想让派对燃爆
At first we thought the DJ was just getting the party started,
没想到是真的火灾
but it actually was.
总之我们会尽量不保持安静的
Anyway, we'll try not to keep it down.
下一个是谁  我已经洗干净了
Okay, who's next? I washed it out.
不许再有人呕吐进这玩意里了
Nobody else throw up in this thing.
真的不行哦
I mean it.
等我把这杯干了
After I crush this,
你要跟我一起回我宿舍吗
you wanna come back to my dorm room?
我住的是小套房哦
I have a junior suite.
你真贴心  "小"子
You're sweet, Junior.
但我男朋友的年纪都可以当你爹了
but I have a boyfriend who could be your father.
他也可能是我爹  反正我从来没见过我亲爹
He also could be my father, I've never met the man.
扫兴鬼来了  三点钟方向
Uh, Buzzkill, 3:00.
等一下  小年轻
Just a minute, young man.
这里不允许未成年人喝酒
There is no underage drinking here.
这可是大学啊
This is college.
你好
Hello?
是你啊  奥列格
Oh, hi, Oleg.
我又找不着苏菲了
I lost Sophie again.
她就像一串性感的车钥匙
She's like a sexy set of car keys.
不许随便跟人一夜情
No random, uncommitted sex here.
这可是大学啊
This is college.
我有满满一电脑的视频可以证明你是错的
I have a computer full of videos that says you're wrong.
奥列格  我现在没空
Oleg, I can't talk now.
我有自己的事要烦  我不知道宿管去哪儿了
I have my own problems. I don't know where the RA is,
所以我不得不出手去管他们
so I've had to step up.
我们就像禁止学生鬼混的海军陆战队
We're like the Marines of no funny business.
那最好别是大麻烟
That better not be a joint.
没错  果然是  兄弟
Yeah, that's a doobie, brother.
苏菲甚至不让我喂芭芭拉
Sophie won't even let me feed Barbara.
她说父亲没能力胜任这份工作
She says fathers aren't equipped for the job.
她的确说得在理  你没有产奶的能力
Well, she does have a point. You don't have boobs.
有人跟你说过  你真是个扫兴鬼吗
Anyone ever tell you you're a real buzzkill?
我得挂了
I have to go.
我听到拉链拉开的声音
I hear zippers unzipping.
你刚是跟中毒控制中心打电话吗
Were you just on the phone with Poison Control?
我告诉你  史蒂夫死不了
Because I told you, Steve's gonna be fine.
瞧  还喘着气呢吧
See? Breathing, I think.
快把上衣脱了  跟我一起快饮啤酒
Now take off your top and shotgun a beer with me.
麦克斯  我明天就要演讲了
Max, my speech is tomorrow,
再说了  我这件上衣可是广受好评
and this top gets a lot of compliments.
我只是想你在大学里真正享乐一次
I just want you to have fun at college for once.
你就当为了我好吗
Can you do that for me?
我经常为了你做各种事
I do things for you all the time.
还记得有次我告诉你约会对象  放屁的是栗宝吗
You remember when I told your date it was Chestnut that farted.
好吧
Fine.
如果我喝一杯  你能把史蒂夫滚出去
If I have one drink, will you roll Steve out of here
让大家都离开这里吗
and get everyone to leave?
扫兴鬼  扫兴鬼  扫兴鬼
Buzzkill! Buzzkill! Buzzkill!
现在谁才是扫兴鬼呀  小婊砸们
Who's the buzzkill now, bitches?
带坏书呆真是有意义的工作
Corrupting dorks is meaningful work.
谁想看我再度假装上史蒂夫啊
Who wants to see me pretend bang Steve again?
要上就真上
Do it for real!
卡洛琳  你这是在干什么
Caroline, what are you doing?
你应该是最清楚
You of all people should know,
这里不能开派对的人啊
you can't have a party here.
这可是大学啊
This is college.
少啰嗦  小报告妹
Pfft, get off my back, narc.
这是哪位
Ooh, who's this?
我的未婚夫
My fiance.
看来也得赏你一个吻才能扯平
Guess we gotta make it even.
额滴神啊  我爱死大学妹卡洛琳了
Oh, my God, I love College Caroline
简直完胜所有其他版本的卡洛琳
so much more than all other Carolines.
妈蛋  大学真好玩
Damn, college is fun.
很高兴我来了
I'm glad I went.
糟糕  迟了
Oh, no, I'm late!
不可能
That's impossible.
你好几年不做爱  经期肯定超准
You haven't had sex in years.
另外  你看起来像意大利老奶奶
Also, you look like an Italian grandmother.
天啊
Oh, my God!
谁对我下的毒手
Who did this to me?
这算让步了好吗
This was the compromise.
他们本来是要剃你的头发
They wanted to shave your head.
我还有点宿醉
I am still a little drunk,
我想不起来我的演讲内容了
and I forget what was in my speech,
我看起来像是超好看版的伯特·雷诺兹
and I look like a very pretty Burt Reynolds
这全都要怪你
and this is all your fault!
你的言下之意是伯特·雷诺兹本人不好看吗
Is the implication here that Burt Reynolds isn't pretty?
没错  怪我逼你
Yes, it is my fault for forcing you
放开自己享受生活
to have the time of your life
跟男人们寻欢作乐
and make out with those dudes.
麦克斯  你甚至不...
Max, you don't even--
男人们
dudes?
还是复数
Plural?
多少男人
How many dudes?
数到第三个叫切特的就没数了
I lost count after the third Chet.
真不敢相信你会对我做出这种事
I can't believe you did this to me.
其实更像是  你对他们"做"出这种事
It was more like you doing it to them.
麦克斯  我很认真跟你说话呢
Max, I am serious right now.
冷静  路易基
Calm down, Luigi.
麦克斯  我知道你不爽
Max, I know you were mad
杂志采访和我称你为"搭档"这件事
about the Time Out interview and the "partner" thing,
但我真不敢相信你会故意下套害我
but I can't believe you sabotaged me on purpose.
好吧  首先
Okay, first of all,
我对你想法没有这么多
I don't think about you that much.
抱歉我没说你也有功劳
I am sorry I didn't give you credit,
但搞砸这事对我来说  严重太多了
but ruining this for me is so much worse.
这本是我的复出重头戏
This was gonna be my comeback.
我没有不爽
I wasn't mad.
从头到尾只有你在不爽而已
You were the only one upset about it.
我完全不在乎那玩意
I don't care about that stuff.
老实说  我只是想让你尽情享乐而已
Honestly, I just wanted you to have a good time.
我不需要享乐
I didn't need to have a good time.
我需要的是让大家羡慕嫉妒恨
I needed to make people jealous.
现在谁还会对我羡慕嫉妒恨
Who's gonna be jealous of me now?
长不出胡子的家伙吗
Guys that can't grow facial hair?
听着  你在学校成绩很棒
Look, you were great at school
昨晚你在学校玩得也很棒
and last night you were great at having fun at school.
你很幸运了  我只能拥有昨晚
You're lucky. I have last night,
但我永远做不到会读又会玩
but I'll never get to have both.
你在说什么啊
What're you talking about?
你是聪明优等生
You're the smart one.
你该享有成功的时刻
You deserve your moment of triumph,
但你同时也该享有余生不被人称为
but you also deserve not to be Buzzkill Channing
扫兴鬼卡洛琳的权利
for the rest of your life.
你真的没有因为访问的事而不爽吗
You really weren't mad about the interview?
有一点
A little,
但我永远都在不爽你啊
but I'm always a little mad at you.
如果我害到你了  那很抱歉
I'm sorry if I screwed things up.
不必了
You don't have to be.
我的确玩得很开心  麦克斯
I really did have fun, Max.
看看你喜不喜欢我在你奶头上画的傻子眼睛
See if you like the googly-eyes I drew around your nipples.
真有意思  眼珠子的方向还不一样呢
Fun how they go in different directions.
抱歉我们来晚了
Sorry we're late.
我得把大眼睛擦掉  因为画在我的...
I had to scrub the googly-eyes off my--
自行车太多  有点堵了
bicycle traffic.
我们开始吧
Well, let's get started.
我本来应该跟我儿子史蒂夫吃午饭的
I'm supposed to have lunch with my son, Steve.
但昨晚他去派对前  我们俩吵了一架
We had a little fight last night before he left for a party.
如果他发生什么不测  我一定会悲痛欲绝
If anything ever happened to him, I'd be devastated.
希望不是昨晚那个史蒂夫
Praying for a different Steve.
这教室有一半的学生跟你亲热过
Wow, you made out with half the people in this room.
我敢肯定其中一个切特被你搞大肚子了
I'm pretty sure you got one of the Chets pregnant.
卡洛琳·钱宁是沃顿的校友
Caroline Channing is an alumni of Wharton,
同时也是布鲁克林
and also the brains behind
一家成功的新甜品酒吧的策划人
a thriving new dessert bar in Brooklyn,
今天她来说说她的成功创业史
and she is here to tell us how she did it.
对了  提醒一下总在我车后面写"洗我"的同学
Oh, also, um, whoever keeps writing "Wash me" in the back of my car,
洗字应该是三点水
there's no R in wash.
有请卡洛琳
Caroline.
今天非常荣幸来到这里
It is a great honor to be here today.
这所优秀的学校教会我很多东西
I learned a lot at this fine institution.
努力工作  诚实正直
Hard work, integrity,
还有一堆我永远用不上的数学
a lot of math I'll never use.
这里有很多非常聪明的人
There are a lot of smart people here,
但我所认识的最聪明的人
but the smartest person I know,
是跟我在餐厅当服务员的人
I met waiting tables in a diner.
麦克斯  转过来
Max, turn around.
转过脸来
The other way.
我很骄傲地称她为我的搭档
And I am proud to call her my partner.
"拉拉"味有点重
Gay.
我能来这里全拜她所赐
This woman is the reason I'm here today.
应该由她来演讲  她才是我成功的最大原因
She should be giving the speech because she's how I did it.
她叫麦克斯·布莱克
Her name is Max Black.
你这是干什么  你要走了吗
Um, what're you doing? You're leaving?
他们已经够羡慕嫉妒恨了
They're jealous enough,
我想你拥有自己的成功时刻
and I want you to have your moment.
你也该两者兼得
You should get to have both too.
而且我要去吐了
And also, chug-chug has to puke-puke.
那...  好吧
And, uh, all right...
我没有上过大学
I didn't go to college,
但在这里待了一晚后
but after spending some time here,
我想我可以教你们几招
I think I could teach you a few things.